========================================================================================================

Reverse Helpline:  
877-234-7744

Primary Menu
============

Search for:  

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Reverse Mortage Advisors of America collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.reverseloanadvice.com/](http://www.reverseloanadvice.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Reverse Mortage Advisors of America.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. SMS Consent will not be shared with any affiliates or third parties.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Reverse Mortage Advisors of America may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

– To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

– To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Reverse Mortage Advisors of America has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

111 Corporate Dr. #235  
Ladera Ranch, CA. 92694

877-856-8706

info@reverseloanadvice.com

This document was last updated on June 03, 2014

Contact Info
============

111 Corporate Dr. #235  
Ladera Ranch, CA. 92694  
  
Phone: 877-234-7744  

Copyright © 2024 United Pacific Realty and Investment, Inc. DBA Reverse Mortgage Advisors of America. Company NMLS # 118004. All Rights Reserved.  
_This material is not from HUD or FHA and had not been approved by HUD or any government agency._  
  
Web Design by [Point Click Productions](http://www.pointclickproductions.com/)

* 
* 
* 
*
